<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>General on Alan Blount &amp; Family | zeroasterisk</title>
    <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/categories/general/</link>
    <description>Recent content in General on Alan Blount &amp; Family | zeroasterisk</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2015 05:10:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://zeroasterisk.com/categories/general/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Best part of CodepaLOUsa so far…</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2015/04/28/best-part-of-codepalousa-so-far/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2015 05:10:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2015/04/28/best-part-of-codepalousa-so-far/</guid>
      <description>Best part of CodepaLOUsa so far&amp;#8230; sitting next to Douglas Crockford at dinner tonight. Occasionally I&amp;#8217;m the lucky one. (Hope I didn&amp;#8217;t bore him too much)
Anyway &amp;#8211; having a fun time at CodepaLOUsa and hope all other attendees are too.
http://codepalousa.com/schedule</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blount 2011 “Year in Review Letter”</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2011/12/20/blount-2011-year-in-review-letter/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2011 17:20:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2011/12/20/blount-2011-year-in-review-letter/</guid>
      <description>Everyone seems to do a great job of sending out yearly letters around the holidays, so here&amp;#8217;s our attempt.
We collected some of our favorite photos from this year (mostly just the summer and fall) and made this video:
http://animoto.com/play/PXP02w37vyZ60ddGU7vxxg
Go ahead and watch it.
Back already?
It&amp;#8217;s the end of December already and Poppy is almost 4 (01/24) and Oliver is almost 2 (02/02). Last year at this time, we went to Kansas City for Christmas with Alan&amp;#8217;s family and after a long drive on Christmas eve, made it back to Louisville for Christmas with Anita&amp;#8217;s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Poppy is 1000 days old today</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2010/10/20/poppy-is-1000-days-old-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2010 17:02:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2010/10/20/poppy-is-1000-days-old-today/</guid>
      <description>Poppy is 1000 days old today!
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Trip to California</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2009/09/09/our-trip-to-california/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2009 15:22:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2009/09/09/our-trip-to-california/</guid>
      <description>We are home again, from a trip to San Francisco and Sonoma, California. (map)
The trip was for April&amp;#8217;s wedding (Anita&amp;#8217;s sister) to Billie one of our best friends from our three years in Columbus, OH.
We started out by going to Salt Point State Park and camping. We were able to hike to the beautiful (but cold) cliff-lined-coast and watch seals and waves alike. On our way back from camping we visited Fort Ross, the oldest establishment on the west coast, and old Russian trading post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WolframAlpha &amp; Google Chrome OS</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2009/07/08/google-chrome-os/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 16:58:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2009/07/08/google-chrome-os/</guid>
      <description>I recently came across wolframalpha which is really fantastic. It provides a much of data for a very wide variety of searches&amp;#8230; basically the neat part is it&amp;#8217;s conversion of English statements into data-based queries and graphs&amp;#8230; It works across tons and tons of datatypes, including one of the most useful weather reports I&amp;#8217;ve seen&amp;#8230; simple and obvious and useful data across the board. (perhaps I just like graphs too much) It also has good financial data, though I still prefer google finance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Running and Talking and Loud</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2009/06/20/running-and-talking-loud/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2009 03:15:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2009/06/20/running-and-talking-loud/</guid>
      <description>Poppy has stopped walking and is pretty much either running to places, or stumble-running. I&amp;#8217;m sure that&amp;#8217;s an exaggeration, but it is certainly what it seems like.
Likewise, she&amp;#8217;s still babbling incoherently &amp;#8211; but she&amp;#8217;s doing so loudly. Also &amp;#8211; her speech patterns are much closer to English. We don&amp;#8217;t know what she&amp;#8217;s saying, but she sure does and, by god, she means it. Her actual vocabulary has increased to maybe a dozen words and phrases:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Poppy Update, 15.5 months</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2009/05/10/poppy-update-15-and-a-half-months/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2009 16:58:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2009/05/10/poppy-update-15-and-a-half-months/</guid>
      <description>Poppy is starting to really put things together. She&amp;#8217;s long been understanding much more than we would have expected, occasionally doing things we ask her to do which we would never anticipate her doing (like asking her to throw something away in another room, and her doing so). Now she&amp;#8217;s starting to say a few more words, do a few more signs, and saying/signing more clearly.
She&amp;#8217;s had a bit of a rough month, all four of her I-Teeth are coming in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winter Weather hits Louisville</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2009/02/03/winter-weather-hits-louisville/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2009 05:36:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2009/02/03/winter-weather-hits-louisville/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;#8217;s been a crazy winter, the last week. The ice storm which took out most of KY&amp;#8217;s power only kept us out for a couple of days, but still has some friends down. It was crazy to see all of the trees weighed down and drooping, beautiful and terrible. The ice coated everything, and when the wind blew all of the ice-coated limbs and branched clinked with each other.
Here&amp;#8217;s a great photo from a friend of mine, mitch:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photobooth photos from Scott and Tami’s wedding</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2009/01/12/photobooth-photos-from-scott-and-tamis-wedding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2009 16:34:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2009/01/12/photobooth-photos-from-scott-and-tamis-wedding/</guid>
      <description>Scott and Tami had a wonderful wedding in Columbus in late fall 2008. We went with Poppy and my mom Cathy. At the wedding they had a photobooth set up and some of the photos went into a scrapbook and some we took home&amp;#8230; here are the took home ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>we refinanced our mortgage today</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2008/12/17/we-refinanced-our-mortgage-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2008 23:04:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2008/12/17/we-refinanced-our-mortgage-today/</guid>
      <description>We have refinanced (or at least started the process) and locked in at 4.96 after paying a point (it was 5.6 without the point, lenders wanting up-front money and assurance in today&amp;#8217;s market). We are rolling in the point and closing costs into the new loan and we&amp;#8217;ll still be saving $140/month over our current loan (and if we hadn&amp;#8217;t rolled in the costs, it would only have saved us $21/month more).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Mates of State, the story of taking the family on tour</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2008/12/13/the-mates-of-state-the-story-of-taking-the-family-on-tour/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2008 06:35:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2008/12/13/the-mates-of-state-the-story-of-taking-the-family-on-tour/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;#8217;s a great video done by Dan Harris of ABC news on the Mates of State and what the family does when they go on tour.
I love the wholesomeness of it and it fits right in with what I think they would be like.&amp;nbsp; This band is one of my absolute favorites and that&amp;#8217;s only encouraged by this peak into their good parenting and family priorities.
http://abcnews.go.com/video/playerindex?id=6318255
http://www.facebook.com/note.php?note_id=37203373110&amp;amp;ref=mf
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Birth Control Pills Affect Women’s Taste in Men</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2008/12/05/birth-control-pills-affect-womens-taste-in-men/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2008 18:20:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2008/12/05/birth-control-pills-affect-womens-taste-in-men/</guid>
      <description>I thought this was a very interesting article
Birth Control Pills Affect Women&amp;#8217;s Taste in Men
 It’s all about scent. Hidden in a man’s smell are clues about his major histocompatibility complex (MHC) genes, which play an important role in immune system surveillance. Studies suggest that females prefer the scent of males whose MHC genes differ from their own, a preference that has probably evolved because it helps offspring survive: couples with different MHC genes are less likely to be related to each other than couples with similar genes are, and their children are born with more varied MHC profiles and thus more robust immune systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>most of the poppy photos from September are uploaded</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2008/10/19/most-of-the-poppy-photos-from-september-are-uploaded/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2008 05:39:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2008/10/19/most-of-the-poppy-photos-from-september-are-uploaded/</guid>
      <description>I have uploaded most of the photos from September and the first half of October.&amp;nbsp; We have another card to process at some point, but this should be the majority.
September
October

  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wall Street Bailout, explained on Fresh Air’s show Sept. 23, 2008</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2008/09/25/wall-street-bailout-explained-on-fresh-airs-show-sept-23-2008/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2008 02:30:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2008/09/25/wall-street-bailout-explained-on-fresh-airs-show-sept-23-2008/</guid>
      <description>A fantastic interview on Fresh Air regarding our current state of the economy and the proposed bailout plan, where we are encouraged to not look at the details and just buy&amp;#8230;&amp;nbsp;
 The Wall Street Bailout: A Conflict Of Interest?
Henry Paulson: The Treasury secretary&amp;#8217;s $700 billion bailout plan awaits congressional approval.Getty Images
Fresh Air from WHYY,September 23, 2008 · With financial markets in flux and a massive government rescue package in the works, financial reporter and New York Timescolumnist Gretchen Morgenson looks into what&amp;#8217;s involved in the nearly $700 billion deal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kentucky Homeschoolers on Parent’s magazine</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2008/09/21/kentucky-homeschoolers-on-parents-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2008 03:08:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2008/09/21/kentucky-homeschoolers-on-parents-magazine/</guid>
      <description>I saw the following article on a list serve I&amp;#8217;ve been lurking on; a simple overview of personal experience with homeschooling&amp;#8230; but it&amp;#8217;s nice to see local examples get national coverage. Homeschool Diaries: How 3 Families Teach Kids at Home
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The big Louisville windstorm of 2008</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2008/09/16/the-big-louisville-windstorm-of-2008/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2008 14:56:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2008/09/16/the-big-louisville-windstorm-of-2008/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;#8217;re without power, like most of Louisville.
On Sunday afternoon the wind really started picking up. We thought a storm was coming, but we had no idea about the extent. So, stupidly, we went for a walk around the neighborhood with Poppy. As we are walking, we see a small tree go down&amp;#8230; &amp;#8220;whoa &amp;#8211; that&amp;#8217;s crazy&amp;#8221; but you know, it&amp;#8217;s a small tree, perhaps it was just planted&amp;#8230; then we get a little further and we hear a big ripping sound and look back and less than half a block up a huge oak tree has just been pulled up at the roots.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A great article on Jan Arnow’s work in Rwanda</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2008/08/13/a-great-article-on-jan-arnows-work-in-rwanda/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2008 03:46:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2008/08/13/a-great-article-on-jan-arnows-work-in-rwanda/</guid>
      <description>Rwandans look to Louisville for interfaith model
 The Rwandans invited the center&amp;#8217;s executive director, Jan Arnow, to visit their country, where in May, she conducted workshops and discussions with a group that included various faiths, from Muslims to Catholics to Quakers to Pentecostals.
During that visit, she said, group members told her, &amp;#8220;We want to do what your organization does&amp;#8221; &amp;#8212; leading to establishment of the center&amp;#8217;s first branch outside Kentucky.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alan’s Finger is in a Torture Device</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2008/06/26/alans-finger-is-in-a-torture-device-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2008 16:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2008/06/26/alans-finger-is-in-a-torture-device-2/</guid>
      <description>Alan&amp;#8217;s fingers were bent backwards and the ligaments are contracting/scaring&amp;#8230; this is supposed to fix it (uncomfortably).

 Spring-Coil Finger Extension Splint (“Capener” or Wynn Perry)  
Coil springs are placed laterally to the PIP joint and move in line with the joint to increase extension.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Poppy Video at Grannie C’s, early April 2008</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2008/04/11/poppy-video-at-grannie-cs-early-april-2008/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2008 04:01:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2008/04/11/poppy-video-at-grannie-cs-early-april-2008/</guid>
      <description>First, Poppy laughing &amp;#8211; Then a longer segment where Grannie C is talking about stuff that Poppy will do, and then a look around the back deck, and finally a little bit of card playing. (6:44)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update from the snow</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2008/03/09/update-from-the-snow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 19:13:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2008/03/09/update-from-the-snow/</guid>
      <description>Uploaded photos of Poppy for the last several weeks (havn&amp;#8217;t uploaded since early Feb.). You can go through the new ones (march and feb) or just look at the main stream of photos.
It snowed around 7 inches on Friday and Saturday, and we got to play in the snow some, but only very briefly. We both started to daydream about taking Poppy out for sledding adventures and hot chocolate afterwards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New(ish) Job == AO &amp; HH == Great</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2007/11/25/newish-job-ao-hh-great/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2007 17:42:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2007/11/25/newish-job-ao-hh-great/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#8217;ve been working part time for AudiologyOnline for months (after hours and on the weekends), and have finally started there full time as of Nov 15th. It&amp;#8217;s been wonderful, not only has everyone been very nice and supportive, but I&amp;#8217;ve ben able to jump in with both feet and get to work.
It&amp;#8217;s meeting time central. I&amp;#8217;m in LA for a conference on Local Search this week and in Dallas for a company meeting next week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A spider attacks a moth…  in my sink</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2007/10/28/a-spider-attacks-a-moth-in-my-sink/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2007 05:18:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2007/10/28/a-spider-attacks-a-moth-in-my-sink/</guid>
      <description>Checkout these photos of a spider &amp;#8220;taking care of&amp;#8221; a recently caught moth. The color leaves a bit to be desired, but the subject matter afforded an opportunity to play with manual focus on the camera from a close distance&amp;#8230; also it&amp;#8217;s neat to see something like this, zoomed in.
   [Checkout these photos of a spider &amp;#8220;taking care of&amp;#8221; a recently caught moth. The color leaves a bit to be desired, but the subject matter afforded an opportunity to play with manual focus on the camera from a close distance&amp;#8230; also it&amp;#8217;s neat to see something like this, zoomed in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update on the Blounts – Early October 2007</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2007/10/10/update-on-the-blounts-early-october-2007/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2007 18:02:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2007/10/10/update-on-the-blounts-early-october-2007/</guid>
      <description>So, I&amp;#8217;ve been remiss to put anything about us on here recently.&amp;nbsp; I&amp;#8217;m thinking that I might split the blog into two seperate blogs&amp;#8230; one on the Blounts, and one on general stuff I feel like talking about&amp;#8230; 2 weeks.&amp;nbsp; (the perpetual two weeks)
Anyway&amp;#8230;
Anita&amp;#8217;s very pregnant&amp;#8230; always holding her belly and still, gloriously asymptomatic.&amp;nbsp; She&amp;#8217;s working at a low cost mdeical center pharmacy for this month&amp;#8217;s rotation.&amp;nbsp; not very interesting for her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back in Louisville, after family visitation</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2007/07/25/back-in-louisville-after-family-visitation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2007 17:35:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2007/07/25/back-in-louisville-after-family-visitation/</guid>
      <description>Well we made it back to Lou. after going to a family reunion in Arkansas and then visiting family in Texas.(photos)
We&amp;#8217;ve now rolled over 140,000 miles on our Honda CRV (1997) and it&amp;#8217;s doing great. &amp;nbsp;We are nothing but happy with that vehicle.
Anita&amp;#8217;s doing well. &amp;nbsp;She&amp;#8217;s had some &amp;#8220;symptoms&amp;#8221; of pregnancy, but for the most part she&amp;#8217;s avoided most of the typical complaints. &amp;nbsp;She attributes the lack morning sickness to vitamine B6 and the lack of fatigue to being on vacation and napping all the time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>post move to louisville</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2007/06/14/post-move-to-louisville/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2007 14:45:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2007/06/14/post-move-to-louisville/</guid>
      <description>We have spent the last several days moving way too many boxes and things from columbus, oh to louisville, ky. We a glad to be donea nd back at work&amp;#8230; well&amp;#8230; mostly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Firebug is the best tool for AJAX web developers</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2007/05/10/firebug-is-the-best-tool-for-ajax-web-developers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2007 20:27:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2007/05/10/firebug-is-the-best-tool-for-ajax-web-developers/</guid>
      <description>Firebug is a fantastic Firefox Add-On which allows realtime viewing and editing of a page&amp;#8217;s DOM, CSS, etc. as well as net usage reports, and even JS timing and profiling.
If you work on the web, it&amp;#8217;s well worth your time to familiarize yourself with this tool.
Here&amp;#8217;s a video presentation: YUI Theater: Joe Hewitt, Welcome to Firebug 1.0 » Yahoo! User Interface Blog &amp;#8211; summary
Powered by ScribeFire. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Asylum Street Spankers</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2007/02/16/asylum-street-spankers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2007 19:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2007/02/16/asylum-street-spankers/</guid>
      <description>irreverent videos &amp;#8211; compliments of jason s.
Asylum Street Spankers &amp;#8211; Pussy Cat Song &amp;#8211; (YouTube)
Asylum Street Spankers &amp;#8211; Misc &amp;#8211; (YouTube)
Asylum Street Spankers &amp;#8211; Whatever &amp;#8211; (YouTube)
Asylum Street Spankers &amp;#8211; Winning the War on Drugs &amp;#8211; (YouTube)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The life and strife of a web developer/designer</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2007/02/12/the-life-and-strife-of-a-web-developerdesigner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2007 19:52:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2007/02/12/the-life-and-strife-of-a-web-developerdesigner/</guid>
      <description>The life and strife of a web developer/designer, as an animated gif.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>looking for a job – web development / project managment</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2007/01/09/looking-for-a-job-web-development-project-managment/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2007 19:24:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2007/01/09/looking-for-a-job-web-development-project-managment/</guid>
      <description>As you can see, I&amp;#8217;m looking into my options for employment. I have a few leads, but would like to explore all of my options&amp;#8230; at least all of the options I can get in quickly, as I&amp;#8217;d like to have a choice made by late January.
 1-page resume 2-page resume  Ideally, I&amp;#8217;d like to find a position which afforded me the opportunity to manage, design, and develop web-based projects / solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick little update – greyhound to louisville</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2007/01/07/quick-little-update-greyhound-to-louisville/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2007 15:33:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2007/01/07/quick-little-update-greyhound-to-louisville/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#8217;ve been very remiss at updating the blog here&amp;#8230; I&amp;#8217;ve had lots of good family time and some travels, some interesting stories and what-not.
but no&amp;#8230; I&amp;#8217;ve not been updating with anything important&amp;#8230; and I&amp;#8217;m apparently not going to start&amp;#8230;&amp;nbsp; Here&amp;#8217;s a very minor update:
I&amp;#8217;m getting on a greyhound bus today from Columbus to Louisville.&amp;nbsp; Going to a few &amp;#8220;in-the-office meetings&amp;#8221; and also to help Karen and Bryan (Anita&amp;#8217;s Mom &amp;amp; Stepfather) as they frantically get moved from their house in the suberbs to their Victorian house in Old Louisville.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Police brutality – an email from Jason E. (spoon)</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2006/11/22/police-brutality-an-email-from-jason-e-spoon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2006 21:25:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2006/11/22/police-brutality-an-email-from-jason-e-spoon/</guid>
      <description>A great but disturbing email sent by my friend Jason E. (spoon):
 November 14th, 2006: A student is tasered five times while in police custody while in the library at UCLA. The cops tase him, not because he&amp;#8217;s fighting them, but because he is (non-violently) refusing to walk out of the library with them.&amp;nbsp; Note that the cop says, &amp;#8220;Stand up or you&amp;#8217;ll get tased again.&amp;#8221;&amp;nbsp;
Of anything on this video that comment really sickens me the most.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>jamglue – tightness!</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2006/11/17/jamglue-tightness/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2006 19:20:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2006/11/17/jamglue-tightness/</guid>
      <description>Jamglue &amp;#8211; Glue it to the man:
This is a fantastic tool &amp;#8211; to multi-track audio from a collaboartive environment with slick controls and a great/simple user interface.
 http://www.jamglue.com/people/zeroasterisk screencast tutorial http://blog.jamglue.com/ http://jamglue.com/  I just wonder who has time to make such a cool site&amp;#8230; ther interface required would not be simple to whip together.&amp;nbsp; I&amp;#8217;m impressed.
Get it while it&amp;#8217;s beta/hot/free&amp;#8230;
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>vote – and know who you are votting for</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2006/11/07/vote-and-know-who-you-are-votting-for/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2006 18:45:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2006/11/07/vote-and-know-who-you-are-votting-for/</guid>
      <description>don&amp;#8217;tvote.com &amp;#8211; OH
go vote &amp;#8211; you voting can&amp;#8217;t hurt anything, not voting might.
 
 
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marea &amp; DJ are wed, HH3 rocked</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2006/10/31/marea-dj-are-wed-hh3-rocked/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2006 02:39:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2006/10/31/marea-dj-are-wed-hh3-rocked/</guid>
      <description>Marea and DJ&amp;#8217;s wedding on Saturday Oct. 28th was wonderful.&amp;nbsp; The wedding proper was at ~1pm at her father&amp;#8217;s house in the Tyler Park area.&amp;nbsp; It was supposed to be a very small event, which still ended up being 60+ people.&amp;nbsp; It was an hour of hanging out, then 10 minutes of ceremony, and then an hour of eating and hanging out some more.&amp;nbsp; The ceremony was basically: &amp;#8220;we are all happy to be here&amp;#8230; do you, and you?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Praise to Alan</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2006/10/26/praise-to-alan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2006 15:27:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2006/10/26/praise-to-alan/</guid>
      <description>I would like to take a moment and give praise to Alan. For those who know him, know that he is awesomely quicky, white and nerdy. It gets better when you live with him! I have come home after a bad day several times this quarter, and he has cleaned. We&amp;#8217;re not talking just dishes &amp;#8211; we&amp;#8217;re talkin dishes, sweeping, mopping, cat box, laundry, the whole nine yards. He does these things even though he&amp;#8217;s been working all day and probably hasn&amp;#8217;t had a much better day than I have.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iddybud: The Buck Stops with Bush</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2006/10/12/iddybud-the-buck-stops-with-bush/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2006 20:57:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2006/10/12/iddybud-the-buck-stops-with-bush/</guid>
      <description>Iddybud: The Buck Stops with Bush:
 What we have done in Iraq &amp;#8211; the way we went about this venture &amp;#8211; is something I&amp;#8217;m sure that President Bush now regrets, even though he&amp;#8217;d never admit it. We have a strategic nightmare on our hands, and we also have citizens of Iraq &amp;#8211; not al Qaeda, but citizens &amp;#8211; murdering one another. The children in the photo you see above are real.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My company has a new CEO</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2006/09/26/my-company-has-a-new-ceo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2006 20:01:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2006/09/26/my-company-has-a-new-ceo/</guid>
      <description>Here is a link to an article which paints a less than favorable picture of her.
Watch the stock with interest&amp;#8230; but you might not want to invest just yet. (note one of the comments that she was associated w/ the Enron disaster)
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mates of State &amp; Dresdon Dolls –  some videos were found….</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2006/09/15/mates-of-state-dresdon-dolls-some-videos-were-found/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2006 21:10:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2006/09/15/mates-of-state-dresdon-dolls-some-videos-were-found/</guid>
      <description>I got an email to view a video on mtvu.com, but thier crappy player wouldn&amp;#8217;t work on windows XP pro 64&amp;#8230;&amp;nbsp; so, I went looking for other videos by them:
 For the Actor &amp;#8211; Mates of State &amp;#8211; Google Video Mates of State &amp;#8212; Ha Ha &amp;#8211; Google VideoMates of State &amp;#8211; Goods (Its All In Your Head) &amp;#8211; Google Video  That&amp;#8217;s all the MOS I could find&amp;#8230; though there was a funny &amp;#8220;dancing to&amp;#8221; video here and a video commentary: { Mates Of State &amp;#8220;Fraud In The 80&amp;#8217;s&amp;#8221; with director commentary by Arno Salters }.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nuclear weapons, still.</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2006/08/07/nuclear-weapons-still/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2006 20:29:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2006/08/07/nuclear-weapons-still/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#8217;m not nearly as anti-nuclear as most of my socially conceious friends&amp;#8230; at least as it relates to nuclear power and research. That said, I&amp;#8217;m seriously worried about the &amp;#8220;bigger stick&amp;#8221; theory as it escelates into&amp;#8230; well&amp;#8230; the upper ranges of weaponry we&amp;#8217;ve had for a few decades. Though we&amp;#8217;ve been sitting on (or making more) weapons and not really attacking with them (just testing them)&amp;#8230; they exist to be used and can be within minutes from right now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>so, uh… yeah… i admire Matthias Wandel</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2006/07/05/so-uh-yeah-i-admire-matthias-wandel/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2006 16:17:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2006/07/05/so-uh-yeah-i-admire-matthias-wandel/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;#8217;t often randomly surf for people&amp;#8230; but this guy [Matthias Wandel] wrote some software I was using (for the first time, about 5-6 years ago) [jhead] and I randomly browsed over to his personal site and thought he was really (really) cool&amp;#8230; Neat projects and inventions, done both logically and creatively (a combination I admire and strive for, though which I tend to exhibit to a lessor degree).
he came up in conversation again today and so I found his site again and found this page (among others) which just makes me go all warm and fuzzy:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>the one that got away</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2006/06/29/the-one-that-got-away/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2006 14:25:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2006/06/29/the-one-that-got-away/</guid>
      <description>I had written a decent post about freedom of speech and that it is mostly a facade, but even that facade is wonderful&amp;#8230; but the post got lost in the ether (more accuratly, my computer rebooted for unknown reasons).
Anyway, here are the news articles prompting the previous post:
 Secret government or a free press?{#r-1_0} &amp;#8220;flag desecration is an unacceptable form of political protest&amp;#8221; &amp;#8212; U.S. SEN. BILL FRIST » Senate Rejects Flag Desecration Amendment  And I ended up reading a chain of wikipedia articles which went something like:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moonlight Kayaking, then family</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2006/06/12/moonlight-kayaking-then-family/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2006 18:32:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2006/06/12/moonlight-kayaking-then-family/</guid>
      <description>Friday, Anita and I went to Bardstown, Ky to go &amp;#8220;Moonlight Kyaking&amp;#8221; with Theresa and some of her Rugby Teammates/friends [link].
Before we got there we swung by the Jim Beam plant (thinking it was where Myra did a bunch of cool carpentry work, but it wasn&amp;#8217;t) and then the Bernheim Forrest. Bernheim has always been a great place to get back to nature a bit, but it&amp;#8217;s gotten a lot nicer&amp;#8230; the visitor&amp;#8217;s center is amazing, and all the displays and trails we saw, were flawless.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>alan is 10,000 days old today</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2006/06/04/alan-is-10000-days-old-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2006 16:22:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2006/06/04/alan-is-10000-days-old-today/</guid>
      <description>I have really slacked on the the posting recently&amp;#8230; I&amp;#8217;ve had a good amount to talk about, but haven&amp;#8217;t had the motivation to write anything. (at least none that coincides with available time)
I&amp;#8217;ve played a lot of [I have really slacked on the the posting recently&amp;#8230; I&amp;#8217;ve had a good amount to talk about, but haven&amp;#8217;t had the motivation to write anything. (at least none that coincides with available time)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post Houston visit</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2006/05/20/post-houston-visit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2006 19:47:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2006/05/20/post-houston-visit/</guid>
      <description>I have put off writing something in response to my visit to Houston, Tx. Partially due to laziness, and perhaps partially to allow more time for settling of experience&amp;#8230; mostly laziness, I suspect.
I was there from May 10th &amp;#8211; 17th, 2006.
About half of the reason I went was simply to have a vacation. It was a chaotic time at work for the prior 2 months and after working many 70 hour weeks in a row&amp;#8230; it was time to do something else.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>on: 911 Loose Change 2nd Edition with extra footage</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2006/05/05/on-911-loose-change-2nd-edition-with-extra-footage/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2006 21:27:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2006/05/05/on-911-loose-change-2nd-edition-with-extra-footage/</guid>
      <description>Text of an email I spammed to just about everyone I have an address for:
 ===INTRO==============
I&amp;#8217;m sorry to have sent what could be considered propaganda to you. I believe it&amp;#8217;s well put together and raises very important questions, furthermore validating those questions and invalidating many official responses with evidence. Because of this, and because it&amp;#8217;s so easy to send around (just a link to a video) I have decided to send it to just about everyone in my address book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>flickr is really… really cool…</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2006/03/12/flickr-is-really-really-cool/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2006 02:57:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2006/03/12/flickr-is-really-really-cool/</guid>
      <description>I have setup a Flickr account/profile and played with it some&amp;#8230;&amp;nbsp; it&amp;#8217;s totally awesome.&amp;nbsp; I&amp;#8217;ve heard of it for years, but haven&amp;#8217;t needed anything like it, since I have gallery installed on a server on which I have nigh&amp;#8217;-unlimited storage space&amp;#8230;&amp;nbsp;
Anyway &amp;#8211; that&amp;#8217;s my excuse for being slow to jump on this bandwagon&amp;#8230;&amp;nbsp; I&amp;#8217;m here now.
The only question is deciding if I want to make the switch and pay for an unlimited account&amp;#8230; then move all the photos I have in gallery into flickr&amp;#8230; and worry about when their server goes down or looses all of my photos (not that such is likely, but less under my control).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lord of war – response</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2006/02/25/lord-of-war-response/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2006 02:18:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2006/02/25/lord-of-war-response/</guid>
      <description>I just got done watching the movie: Lord of War (2005)
I think it was a good film, in the vane of &amp;#8220;blow&amp;#8221; and &amp;#8220;traffic&amp;#8221; but with a different angle and a semi-moral overtone.&amp;nbsp; The best part, IMO, is the ending and the open and blatant fact that when it comes to weapons of any sort, the US not only has the most, but sells the most &amp;#8211; seemingly to anyone else.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>attempt at positive spin on mountaintop removal</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2005/12/30/attempt-at-positive-spin-on-mountaintop-removal/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2005 19:39:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2005/12/30/attempt-at-positive-spin-on-mountaintop-removal/</guid>
      <description>Phil sent me a link to the article [Appalachian town mining for land] which is talking about the removal of mountains by a coal mining company as a positive thing&amp;#8230; to some it may well be &amp;#8211; but as coal mining companies are notorious for their environmental horrors, and as we are already starting to &amp;#8220;run low&amp;#8221; on mountains that have been created (tectonically) for thousands of years &amp;#8212; perhaps people ought to think about keeping their mountains around as long as they can (which is basically until a mining company finds something they want in said mountain).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanksgiving</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2005/11/24/thanksgiving/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2005 21:56:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2005/11/24/thanksgiving/</guid>
      <description>Here is my requisite turkeyday post. Anita had to work her last day today, so we are in Columbus still. She plans on not working until this summer. I&amp;#8217;ve been encouraging her to do this&amp;#8230; though her ~10 hours of work a week doesn&amp;#8217;t sound like much, since she does ~60 hours a week of school work &amp;#8211; a few extra hours to relax would be welcome.
We will be driving to Louisville tonight after anita is off work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>secrets are stupid, and so is the Kansas board of Education</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2005/11/09/56/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2005 08:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2005/11/09/56/</guid>
      <description>After reading the article: CIA prisons leak &amp;#8216;to be probed&amp;#8217;, I was overcome one specific emotion: unease (fear)&amp;#8230; The fact that there are secret prisons and nobody knows about them scares the hell out of me.
Basically, if I was taken to prison for thinking our current government sucks (or for being too cynical or too naive), I would want people to know about it&amp;#8230; and hopefully make a fuss&amp;#8230; you know&amp;#8230; maybe get to talk to a lawyer and not be tortured.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jenifire went to Peru (who knew?)</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2005/11/01/jenifire-went-to-peru-who-knew/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2005 17:33:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2005/11/01/jenifire-went-to-peru-who-knew/</guid>
      <description>So, in August, apparentally, Jeno went to Peru&amp;#8230; It looks like she toured the countryside and hiked up mountains&amp;#8230; went to the amazon rainforest, boated across pink-dolphin infested waters, and got friendly with sheep and mules alike.
I want the full story&amp;#8230; if i get it I will post it somewhere&amp;#8230;. perhaps I can convince her to start a blog of her own&amp;#8230;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>recent spoon photos</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2005/10/24/recent-spoon-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2005 22:45:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2005/10/24/recent-spoon-photos/</guid>
      <description>Spoon has posted some new (depending on when you last looked) photos&amp;hellip; here are some of my favorites:
dj spoon, weed airport, an attractive salad, and 40 oz of art.
Now playing: [Tom Waits][5] &amp;#8211; [Nighthawks at the Diner &amp;#8211; Nighthawk Postcards][6]
[5]: http://phobos.apple.com/WebObjects/MZSearch.woa/wa/advancedSearchResults?artistTerm=Tom Waits [6]: http://phobos.apple.com/WebObjects/MZSearch.woa/wa/advancedSearchResults?songTerm=Nighthawks at the Diner - Nighthawk Postcards&amp;amp;artistTerm=Tom Waits</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>za1 theme in development</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2005/09/25/za1-theme-in-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2005 06:42:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2005/09/25/za1-theme-in-development/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on a comprehensive theme, currently called za1 (very exciting name, eh?).&amp;nbsp; I will be mapping the components of my site into that theme (instead of hacking the themes of the components of my site to look kindof like each other).
The themes are driven primarily by CSS, and done in such a way as to allow simple variations in how things should look&amp;hellip; there will be an &amp;ldquo;options&amp;rdquo;&amp;nbsp;selector on the top-right and it will allow you to easily choose theme options and it saves your options as a cookie (if you allow the cookie) or session variables if your don&amp;rsquo;t allow the cookies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rita Update &amp; Anit-War Protest Story</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2005/09/24/rita-update-anit-war-protest-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2005 16:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2005/09/24/rita-update-anit-war-protest-story/</guid>
      <description>Rita Update:
Rita, as a Category 3 hurricane (120 mph) made landfall at 2:30 a.m. CDT today in extreme southwest Louisiana between Sabine Pass and Johnson&amp;#8217;s Bayou, La. Port Arthur, Texas, clocked maximum wind gusts of 116 mph, while Beaumont, Texas, measured 105 mph. Cameron, La., reported a gust to 112 mph before the anemometer failed. Storm surge flooding of up to 15 feet probably occured just east of where the eye thundered ashore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rita – hurricane in Houston</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2005/09/22/rita-hurricane-in-houston/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2005 21:33:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2005/09/22/rita-hurricane-in-houston/</guid>
      <description>An Email to/from Cathy (my mom) who lives in Houston, in response to the coming hurricane everyone is freaking out about (because of the recent Katrina problems in New Orleans).
From Alan
 dear houston clan:
After calling mom 6+ times, and never getting through, anita suggested I email her&amp;#8230; and due to the subject matter, I decided to email all of you.
come to columbus if you want to escape the hurricane.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post Labor Day &amp; and an interesting story</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2005/09/06/post-labor-day-and-an-interesting-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2005 15:52:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2005/09/06/post-labor-day-and-an-interesting-story/</guid>
      <description>Saturday Anita had to work, but Phil, Sarah, Jess, and Phil&amp;rsquo;s friend Tom came over and played Mao&amp;nbsp;1.&amp;nbsp; It&amp;rsquo;s a great game &amp;ndash; and surprisingly effective at bringing about a represive dictatorial feel in the players (who thought that could be so much fun?).&amp;nbsp;
We played a variant where after winning 3 rounds you could make up your own rule&amp;hellip;&amp;nbsp; my personal favorite was (my rule): you have to use rapper hands whenever you call penalty on someone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kitten Update</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2005/08/19/kitten-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2005 04:24:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2005/08/19/kitten-update/</guid>
      <description>I took the kittens to the vet yesterday. It turns out they&amp;#8217;re only 6 weeks old and they are both males. We have also decided on names for them. The black one is henceforth Thebe, and the white and orange one is Io. These are the names of 2 of Jupiter&amp;#8217;s moons, so we were able to stick with the science theme afterall!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>kittens arrive</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2005/08/16/kittens-arrive/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2005 02:06:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2005/08/16/kittens-arrive/</guid>
      <description>We have kittens.

That&amp;#8217;s right, it&amp;#8217;s cute-fest-2005 in our apartment right now. We got a pair of 8 6 week old kittens on Sunday from Anita&amp;#8217;s co-worker who got them dumped on her by her mom. They are a brother (black) and sister (white &amp;amp; orange) and have very quickly bonded with Anita and I&amp;#8230; they are ok with Nova, but she&amp;#8217;s not yet ok with them. Nova actually submitted to them, belly up and looking away; our guard dog proving her grit once again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>April is ok after the 7.2 magnitude earthquake</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2005/08/16/april-is-ok-after-the-72-magnitude-earthquake/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2005 08:18:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2005/08/16/april-is-ok-after-the-72-magnitude-earthquake/</guid>
      <description>From an email from April:
_However, I did want to let everyone know that I am
safe and perfectly whole after this morning&amp;#8217;s earthquake. For those of you
who have no idea what I&amp;#8217;m talking about, a 7.2 magnitude earthquake hit
Japan at 11:46 this morning and I was a mere 60 some-odd kilometers south of
its center of its origin. It&amp;#8217;s on the front page of BBC, CNN, MSN-NBC, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>japan backlog finished / Ryka’s bithday</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2005/08/05/japan-backlog-finished-rykas-bithday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2005 15:45:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2005/08/05/japan-backlog-finished-rykas-bithday/</guid>
      <description>Well, I&amp;#8217;m finally done with updating the backlogged Japan blog entries. It was something I kept putting off, but I&amp;#8217;m real glad I did it &amp;#8211; the posts are kinda long, but it&amp;#8217;s as much for my memory of the trip as anyone else&amp;#8217;s (sorry).
 I&amp;#8217;m impressed that within 45 minutes of uploading the lastest batch of photos, some of them have been looked at 4 times already&amp;#8230; I know I&amp;#8217;m just getting lucky, but it still nice to know someone is looking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anita has hair / I have pictures</title>
      <link>https://zeroasterisk.com/2005/07/13/anita-has-hair-i-have-pictures/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2005 22:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeroasterisk.com/2005/07/13/anita-has-hair-i-have-pictures/</guid>
      <description>Anita&amp;#8217;s hair is finally long enough to put into psuedo-pig-tails! glory glory&amp;#8230;
[Anita&amp;#8217;s hair is finally long enough to put into psuedo-pig-tails! glory glory&amp;#8230;
]1
Also, while you are looking at that photo, look around the friends 2005 photos &amp;#8211; there are finally a few other pictures besides documentation of my various hair styles&amp;#8230;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>